{
    "subject": "resource/The_Penguins_of_Madagascar",
    "predicate": "property/showName",
    "object": "The Penguins of Madagascar",
    "human_readable": "The show name of The Penguins of Madagascar is The Penguins of Madagascar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9814642071723938,
            "question": "Name the cartoon about penguins from Madagascar."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9010239839553833,
            "question": "Which TV show centers around a group of Madagascar penguins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8466266393661499,
            "question": "What is the name of the show about penguins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6770048141479492,
            "question": "What is the title of the animated series featuring penguins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.471750408411026,
            "question": "What is the name of the show where Skipper leads his penguin team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42360955476760864,
            "question": "Which animated series features a famous penguin named Skipper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3928864300251007,
            "question": "Give me the title of the animated series with the penguins Skipper, Kowalski, Rico, and Private."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3923014998435974,
            "question": "What is the name of the popular cartoon about four penguins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38486894965171814,
            "question": "What show features a group of penguins who often go on missions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3612404763698578,
            "question": "Which animated series follows the adventures of four penguin spies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The show name of The Penguins of Madagascar is The Penguins of Madagascar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7045_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What show features a group of penguins who often go on missions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7045_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the popular cartoon about four penguins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7045_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give me the title of the animated series with the penguins Skipper, Kowalski, Rico, and Private.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7045_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7045_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7045_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7045_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7045_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7045_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7045_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7045_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7045_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7045_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7045_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to \"The Penguins of Madagascar\" as the title and name of the animated television series, which directly supports the given statement that the show name is \"The Penguins of Madagascar.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}